Prasenjit Malakar

+91-9863970863 | https://click2jit.github.io/|click2jit@qmail.com

EDUCATION

IGNOU

MASTER OF COMPUTER APPLICATION Dec 2014 | Agartala, India

TRIPURA UNIVERSITY BCA

July 2011 | Kailashahar, Tripura

LINKS

Tryhackme:// click2jit LinkedIn:// click2jit Github:// click2jit Twitter:// click2jit

COURSEWORK

PENETRATION TESTING

Information Gathering (Reconnaissance) Scanning and Enumeration Vulnerability Scanning with Nessus Exploitation Exploit Development (Buffer Overflows) Privilege Escalation Attacking Active Directory

Wireless Penetration Testing

DEGREE

OWASP top 10

Algorithms and Data Structure
Operating Systems
DBMS
Object Oriented Programming
Data Communication and Computer
Networking

SKILLS

TECHNICAL

- Host and Networking Auditing
- Assessment Methodologies
- Host and Networking Penetration Testing
- Web Application Penetration Testing
- Vulnerability Assessment Network Analyzer • Linux • SQL • Metasploit
- Nmap OSINT Security Audit SIEM
- Routing and Switching Networking
- OSI Model

PROGRAMMING

Java • Python • Javascript ¡Query • C • C++ • CSS

SUMMARY

Self-Motivated, quick learner, hard-working, enthusiastic individual seeking a position in the field of Cybersecurity as a Penetration Tester. Professional with 11+ years of experience in network design, escalation support, network and systems administration. Skilled in delivering technical customer support, managing network operations, and maintaining Organization-wide area networks.

EXPERIENCE

GA DIGITAL WEB WORD PVT. LTD. | NETWORK CUM FIELD ENGINEER

Jan 2023 - Present | DM and Collector Office, Unakoti, Tripura

- Responsible for managing lease line connectivity for District's PoPs.
- Proactively monitored network performance and coordinated restoration efforts with lease line vendors in case of disruptions.

WIPRO LIMITED | SENIOR NETWORK CUM FIELD ENGINEER - ADMINISTRATOR

Feb 2018 - Dec 2022 | At National Informatics Centre, Unakoti, Tripura

- Configuration and monitoring of L2 Switches, Routers and IP phones.
- Network Traffic Monitoring using Netflow Analyzer | IP allocation and management of Govt. Offices Under State Wide Area Network (SWAN).
- Prevented unauthorized access to the network, MAC filtering

RENOVISION AUTOMATION SERVICES PVT. LTD. | NETWORK CUM FIELD ENGINEER

July 2017 - Jan 2018 | At National Informatics Centre, Unakoti, Tripura

- Monitoring systems, networks and infrastructure using Nagios.
- Asset Management, Bandwidth Management, Antivirus Log Collection.

WIPRO INFOTECH PVT. LTD. | NETWORK - ASSOCIATE MANAGEMENT

Aug 2012 – June 2017 | At National Informatics Centre, Unakoti, Tripura

• Installation and maintenance of Network devices, Computer Systems, APs

HCL INFOSYSTEM | NETWORK FIELD ENGINEER

Sep 2011 – June 2012 | At National Informatics Centre, Unakoti, Tripura

PROJECTS

PYTHON KEYLOGGER | PYTHON, GITHUB GIST - Link

DISTRICT WEBSITE OF UNAKOTI | S3WAAS, WORDPRESS

www.unakoti.nic.in | NIC Unakoti, Tripura

Developed and maintaing Official Website of Unakoti District, Tripura.

REVENUE COURT CASE MONITORING SYSTEM | JAVA , POSTGRESOL

https://rccms.tripura.gov.in/ | Govt. Of Tripura Developed modules in RCCMS for Tripura Government.

CERTIFICATE

Dec 2023 INE Junior Penetration Tester (eJPT)

Aug 2023 Google Google Cybersecurity Professional Certificate